Hello everyone, welcome to our new daily
podcast, Stocks of the Day,
which features Sher Khan's fundamental research coverage
and includes stocks on the Nifty 200 list.
Stocks
that
generate strong bullish signals for the short term based on technical parameters are
recommended as Stock of the Day. Today's
Stock of the Day is ICS Lumbard General
Insurance. ICS Lumbard General Insurance is
one of India's leading private sector general insurance companies. The
company has a
strong, diversified, and seamless
distribution channel, both online and offline, to serve the needs of individuals, corporates, MSMEs, and government customers. We believe the
company can deliver a RE of 18 to 20% in the medium term.
At the current market price, the stock is trading at 33.2 times F25's
EPS and 27.8 times F26's EPS.
Stock of the Day will provide you with
excellent short-term trading opportunities every day.
Every Morning Sher  Khan's